Guide to the Yale Miscellaneous Manuscripts Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale Miscellaneous Manuscripts Folios: Alphabetical
  - (A-K)
    - Baldwin, William Pitt, 1891, 1923 (Box IA)
    - Barnard, Henry, 1853, 1886 (Box IA)
    - Barnes, Henry Burr, (Jr.), 1897, 1899 (Box IB)
    - Barnes, Thomas Cunliffe, 1932 (Box IB)
    - Bartlett, Philip Golden, 1885 (Box IB)
    - Beach, John Kimberly, 1896, 1913, 1921 (Box IB)
    - Bigelow, Russell Anson, 1884-1886 (Box IB)
    - Boltwood, Thomas, 1866 (Box IC)
    - Brown, Charles Reynolds, 1862, 1889, 1950 (Box IC)
    - Browning, Philip Embury, 1886, 1895 (Box IC)
    - Bryant, Horatio, 1836, 1886 (Box IC)
    - Bull, William Tillingmast, 1886, 1902, 1914 (Box IC)
    - Carter, Leslie, 1851 (Box ID)
    - Catlin, Benjamin C., 1825 (Box ID)
    - Chandler, T. B., 1766-1776 (Box ID)
    - Channing, C., 1869 (Box ID)
    - Churchill, William, 1896 (Box ID)
    - Colton, Henry M., 1859, 1861 (Box ID)
    - Currier, Andrew, 1876-1889, 1918 (Box ID)
    - DeForest Dickinson, William C., 1885 (Box IE)
    - Ecuador, Central Universidad, Quinto, 1930 (Box IE)
    - Elkin, William L., 1876-1895, 1908-1930 (Box IE)
    - Fellows, Henry Parker, 1872-1873 (Box IF)
    - Fisher, Thomas Rawdon, 1904 (Box IF)
    - Fulton, John F., 1932 (Box IF)
    - Griffin, ?, 1935 (Box I)
    - Hawley, Samuel B., 1887, 1919 (Box IF)
    - Hoppin, James M., 1842-1862, 1893, 1902 (Box IF)
    - Ives, Robert Shoemaker, 1901 (Box IF)
    - Jones, Daniel A., 1901 (Box IF)
    - Karrick, David B., 1907, 1920 (Box IF)
  - (L-Z)
    - Lang, Henry Roseman, 1893, 1897, 1908, 1922, 1927 (Box II)
    - Linsley, George Thomas, 1882, undated (Box II)
    - Moore, William, 1938 (Box II)
    - Moseley, Henry Perkins, 1887, 1890-1902 (Box II)
    - Nichols, Effingham H., 1868, 1890 (Box II)
    - Nichols, S., 1880 (Box II)
    - Orton, John Jay, 1847-1851 (Box II)
    - Perkins, Nathaniel, 1844 (Box II)
    - Ph[o]enix Library, [1806?] (Box II)
    - Rand, Gordon Loring, 1908 (Box II)
    - Reed, J. Verner, 1950-1951 (Box II)
    - Reynolds, William Augustus, 1863 (Box II)
    - Rockwood, Charles, 1857, 1906-1914 (Box II)
    - Ross, Baldwin, 1854 (Box II)
    - Runde, Sister Alberic, 1932 (Box II)
    - Sanford, Annie B., 1906 (Box II)
    - Sanford, Charles F., 1874 (Box II)
    - Sanford, Charles P., 1878-1894, 1906 (Box II)
    - Schlesinger, Frank, 1887-1940, 1961 (Box II)
    - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1871-1872 (Box II)
    - Sheppard, Walter Bradley, 1883 (Box II)
    - Todd, Eli, [1880?] (Box II)
    - Van Doren, Carl, undated (Box II)
    - Webster, Charles, 1862-1865 (Box II)
    - Webster, John R., 1857-1868 (Box II)
    - Williams, Arthur Shaler, 1897, 1904 (Box II)
    - Williams, Ralph O., 1865, 1886 (Box II)
    - Woodward, John Butler, 1877 (Box II)
    - Yale University/Harvard University, 1936 (Box II)
    - Zantzinger, Clarence C., 1919-1923 (Box II)
    - Unidentified, 1774 (Box II)
- Yale Miscellaneous Manuscripts Folios: Numerical
  - No. 102A: Le Conte, Porter (1817-1847): 1 ALS to his family, 1840 January (Box III)
    See also: Box 37, No. 102.
  - No. 126: Porter, Jacob, 1802-1831, undated (Box III)
  - No. 140: Kingman, Edward Lyman, 1904, 1906 (Box III)
  - No. 224: Brown, Frank E., 1922, 1938, 1953, 1964, 1967, 1977, 1983 (Box III)
  - No. 231: Harwood, Forest Henry, 1839 (Box III)
  - No. 276: Yale photograph, Circa 1930 (Box III)
  - No. 277: Yale paper dolls, 1983 (Box III)
  - No. 278: Yale University Register, World's Fair, St. Louis, 1904 (Box IV)
  - No. 279: Mounted prints, early nineteenth century (Box V)
- Addition
  - "An Electro Magnet" drawing from Kinsgley Trust Association, circa 1898 (Box 78)
  - Crosby RM sketch (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Doggett, N on account of the treatment accorded him..., 1779 July 26 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Dunn, Fred W. original drawing for the New Haven plate (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Fraternal greeting to the Yale chapter of Alpha Delta Phi (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Galvin RW Benjamin Franklin Clark, 1941 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Grand Army of the Republic Certificate John E. Clark, 1873 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Koehler, H original drawing of a Pierson tie, 1947 November (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Maxwell Party Yale University dramatic association poster (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Moran, Percy Founding of Yale watercolor, circa 1947 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Niemeyer self-portrait (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Ordre National de la Legion D'Honneur certicate, 1938 October 25 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Osborn, O.T. masonic certificate (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Passport issued to J.A. Root (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Petition regarding compulsory chapel, 1926 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - R. Osborn Alumni magazine cover, 1928 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Robinson, Samuel to Henry Robinson correspondence, 1817 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - 7 drawings by unknown artist on football received from Yale Club of New York, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Tourtell Serenade (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Yale Students as bulldogs (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Yale University class of 1803 copies, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Yale University Divinity School class of 1921 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Phi Delta Theta constitution (Folder 79)
  - Schlesingerdiploma (Folder 80)
  - Yale Bowl press stand assignment, 1931-10-31 (Folder 81)
  - Signatures of the class of 1911 (Folder 82)
  - Drawings for the Yale Record, 1922 (Folder 83)
  - US Sanitary Commission tabulation of examination of individuals (Folder 84)